(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T23:15:49.890152",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival 2026
[Title: FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival 2026]
I'm Fuwawa!
And Mococo!
Bau! Bau!
FUWAMOCO!
Ruffians!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together
Lifetime Showtime
Anytime Bau Bau!
Yeah, future is bright
Yeah...
Yeah, together we are
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Lifetime!
FUWA!
MOCO!
Bau Bau!
My heart n' soul n' tail are FUWAWA
I'm so fluffy that even I could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that I wanna keep safe
FUWA!
MOCO!
I love being tricky, doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies, don't need no leashes for me
I love lots of walkies,
don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy Mococo will follow you anywhere
FUWAMOCO together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together
Lifetime Showtime
Anytime Bau Bau!
一生涯 sing with you
Forever and ever, sing with you
Stars wink, moon spotlight, furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together
Lifetime Showtime
Anytime Bau Bau!
Yeah, future is bright
Yeah...
Yeah, together we are
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Bau! Woooo...
Bau!
Way back then, all locked up, stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away
Bau!
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz, we're meant to be free
Moco!
Make a break for it, it's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement
dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin'
but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why
いつだって It's that day!
Always, it's that day!
Lifetime! Showtime! Not tomorrow! Bau bau!
一生涯 Walk with you!
Forever and ever, walk with you!
Good times and bad times, it doesn't matter!
いつだって It's that day!
Always, it's that day!
Lifetime! Showtime! Everyday! Bau bau!
Yeah, 二人は
Yeah, together we are...
Happy lucky puppy sisters!
FUWAMOCO Bau bau! Everybody, bau bau!
Hallo hallo bau bau! Everybody, bau bau!
ダメダメノンノン！ Don't touch the ears!
No, no! Don't touch the ears!
もふもふノンノン！ Don't touch the tail!
Fluffy fluffy, no, no! Don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ！ フワワだよ！ Bau!
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! Bau!
フワワじゃないよ！ モココだよ！ Bau!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo! Bau!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! Bau!
And together, we're... FUWAMOCO!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime 一緒にいたい
It's showtime, wanna be together
It's showtime 一緒にいたいよ
ふわふわ もこともこ Hand in hand with you
Fuwa-fuwa, moco-moco, hand in hand with you
Bring your smile, rain or shine
We'll protect it, won't forget our pledge to you
It's showtime 一緒にいたい
It's showtime, wanna be together
Lifetime Showtime anytime bau bau!
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau-bau!
一生涯 Sing with you
Forever and ever, sing with you
Stars wink, Moon spotlight, Furr-ever glow
It's showtime 一緒にいたいよ
It's showtime, wanna be together
Lifetime Showtime anytime bau bau!
Lifetime, showtime, anytime, bau-bau!
And...
Together, we're... fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Let's hear you! 最後だよ！
Let's hear you! It's the last part!
FUWA! MOCO!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
MOCO! MOCO!
FUWAMOCO bau! FUWAMOCO bau! Bau!
Ruffians! Bau bau!
Welcome to...
FUWAMOCO Wacha Wacha Birthday Festival!
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate our birthday with us, Ruffians!
始まりました！
It has begun!
今日は3Dライブに来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for coming to our 3D live today!
Well, to continue on from yesterday's variety show shenanigans...
...today we have a 3D concert!
Can you believe it? It's already been three years!
Right! Our third birthday, and whole three years!
But Mococojyan, we can't forget the really important thing, right?
Oh? The introductions!
Yes! Okay!
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Mococo!
We are Hololive English's Advent's twin demon guard dog sisters!
Together, we're FUWAMOCO! Bau bau!
And look! We have an amazing birthday festival stage!
Amazing stage! It's so huge!
And we have so many Ruffians!
Thank you so much, Ruffians!
And such a big stage, too!
Fuwawa, can we... Okay, here we go!
Three, two, one... Bau bau!
It's so big and wide, too!
Thank you, everyone, for being here today!
But singing and dancing today is not just going to be us, right?
No! We're also here with some very special guests, too!
そう、今日はとっても素敵なゲストさんも来てるから、ぜひ楽しみにしててくださいね！
That's right! We have some wonderful guests today, so please look forward to it!
そして、もう一人、謎のゲストさんも…？誰かな？
And, there's also another mysterious guest...? Who could it be?
Bau bau! But, a birthday wouldn't be complete without this, right?
Right! Something very important! I think you know what, but...
Hashtag!
Right up here, you can see our birthday hashtag, hashtag #FWMCbday26!
Please, please post your thoughts, take lots of photos...
そう、ぜひハッシュタグで感想を呟いてください！写真もね！後でポチしに行くからね！
Yes, please tweet your thoughts using the hashtag! Photos too! We'll go look at them later!
We're going to check all of your thoughts after the show!
Yes!
Bau bau!
And also!
We're going to be having a special membership-only concert right after this, so don't miss it, okay?
Yeah! Uh!
最後にはメンバー限定のアンコールライブもありますので、ぜひ見に来てくださいね！
At the very end, we also have a membership-exclusive encore live, so please come watch!
Bau bau! Woah!
You know, it is a concert after all, right? So we get to sing a little more, right? Yeah, yeah!
Wow! Oh, for this next song, I think we need a special guest, right?
Yeah! Uh! Okay, let's call her on together! Okay!
Calli-senpai!
Hey hey hey hey!
みなさん、bau bau!
Everyone, bau bau!
Today only, I am also a dog. Bau bau bau bau! Shinigami dog!
Yeah, shinigami dog! Thank you for inviting me, I'm happy to be here!
What's up, Ruffians?!
But I see you have a pretty nice shirt there, Calli! I do! Wow!
Look at this logo! What does it say? Check it out!
With respect! Respect, respect, respect, with respect! With respect!
You know, it would be pretty cute if we matched, right? Right!
But maybe we'll just go run and we'll get changed real quick for a second? Yeah, okay, entertain them!
Okay, you can do it, I got this. They won't bite, they won't bite. You'll be okay, okay! Bau bau!
Ruffians, welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment! Iku zo!
Ruffians, welcome to Mori Calliope's super special splits challenge segment! Here we go!
I can't... I can't, I'm sorry, I can't do it! I did my best.
Sensensensei! Shinigami-senpai is so cool! But I can't do the split. No, we're matching!
Sen-sen-sen-sen-senpai! Reaper-senpai is so cool! But I can't do the split. No, we're matching!
We're matching, matching! Tripling? Tripling! Tripling! That has a nice ring to it.
This next song is one that Fuwamoco wanted to sing with you for such a long time! Yeah! Yeah!
Something nostalgic, and I think you'll be able to see why. There's some rap in it as well. Oh, yeah!
But it's also very cute, right?
次に歌う曲は、Calli先輩と一緒にずっと歌いたかった大好きな曲です！
The next song we're going to sing is a song we've loved and wanted to sing with Calli-senpai for a long time!
It's both cute, it's cool! Yeah! But I think you know, it shares...
You know, be proud of what you like, right? The important meaning of being proud and being strong about what you like! Yeah, your likes!
You know, like games, anime, idols, figures... Or maybe even VTubers! Oh, nice! Nice!
After all, life is more fun when you're just true to yourself, right? Definitely! I agree!
So we want to sing this song for you, okay?! Okay!
Let's do the title call together, okay? Yes!
聴いてください！ Like! Like! Like!
Please listen! Like! Like! Like!
Like! Like! Like!
Comic! I like it!
Music! I like it!
Game! I like it!
Animation! I like it!
Figure! I like it!
Movie! I like it!
Wonder! I like it!
Hobby! I like it!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Do you like it? I like it!
人生楽しんだモン勝ちの裏技
Life is a trick where whoever enjoys it wins
好きなモノ好きって言えたらそれはスーパーノヴァ
If you can say you like what you like, that's a supernova
快感中枢即maxのover the sun
Pleasure center immediately maxes out over the sun
まるでギターかき鳴らし勝手に歌うバンドマン
Just like a bandman strumming guitar and singing as he pleases
plastic magic 回りくどくてゴメン
Plastic magic, sorry for being roundabout
きっと軸は一緒でしょ？ yes! no reason
Surely our core is the same, right? Yes! No reason
キラめきな魂今すぐ let's make sounds!
Sparkling soul, right now let's make sounds!
キミが部屋に居たって link すればコンサート
Even if you are in your room, if we link up, it's a concert
いつもだって only, lonely... じゃあ手伸ばせ、行くよ
Always only, lonely... So reach out your hand, let's go
I like it! like it! スキになれば
I like it! like it! If you fall in love with it,
きっと全てがカラフルで
surely everything will be colorful,
lucky! lucky! 星屑さえ、光る宝物さ
lucky! lucky! even stardust is a shining treasure.
I like it! like it! キミに会えた、
I like it! like it! I met you,
やっと「今日からヨロシクね」
and finally, "nice to meet you from today."
ほら、キラキラ夢みたい
Look, sparkling like a dream,
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hold you soon.
アレもコレも欲しくて神様に祈ってる
I want this and that, praying to God.
スキでスキでしょうがない
I like it, I like it, I can't help it!
ねえ 好きでしょうがない
Hey, I can't help but love you.
次は何にしようかな
What should we do next?
All back, worldwide, make them all right, yo
Bust out words like, write, like a kid.
360度 パノラマ全方向 大好きの陣
360-degree panorama, all directions, the battlefield of love!
何がどうであれでもいいから 乗り込める 自分のアイテム
No matter what, anything is fine, get on board with your own items...
like a superstar, fire, man
無敵案で 他は大体来世
like a superstar, fire, man!
With an invincible plan, the others can wait till the next life.
望んでる彼もきっと 原石該当 欲しくなるはずなのだよ さあ
Surely even the guy you desire will start wanting the raw gemstone, so come on!
なろうとしてなるもんじゃない 人生楽しんでやろうじゃない
It's not about trying to become it, let's just enjoy life, shall we?
自分に素直であれ スポットライト僕らを照らせ
Be true to yourself, let the spotlight shine on us!
今日も愛を叫ぶだけだ Get up!
Today too, we'll just scream our love, get up!
This is my song for you.
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out,
きっとすべてがミラクルで
everything will surely be a miracle,
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life
夢の物語さ
is a dreamlike story!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I met you,
ずっと離さないでいてね
so don't ever let me go,
ほら キラキラ 虹みたい
Look, sparkling like a rainbow,
世界は回り出す
the world begins to spin!
好き 好き 好きで勝負したいから
I want to challenge you with my love, love, love,
手に入れたい この感情
so I want to possess this emotion.
ためらわないのがいいんでしょ？
It's better not to hesitate, right?
そう 恋をもっと実験
That's right, experiment more with love!
でも それが僕の等身大
But that's just the real, everyday me!
出し切るバシッ世界を確信
Express it fully, BAM, believing in the world,
いわゆる一つの萌え要素
you could say it's a "moe" element!
素直になれたなら Happy Days
If only you could be honest, Happy Days!
I Like It! I Like It! 好きになれば
I Like It! I Like It! If you fall in love,
きっとすべてがカラフルで
everything will surely be colorful,
Lucky! Lucky! 星屑さえ
Lucky! Lucky! Even stardust
光る宝物さ
becomes a shining treasure!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I met you,
「ねー 今日からヨロシクね」
"Hey, let's get along from today on!"
ほら キラキラ 夢みたい
Look, sparkling like a dream,
早く抱きしめたい
I want to hug you soon!
I Like It! I Like It! 手を伸ばせば
I Like It! I Like It! If you reach out,
きっとすべてがミラクルで
everything will surely be a miracle,
Happy! Happy! 日常でさえ
Happy! Happy! Even everyday life
夢の物語さ
is a dreamlike story!
I Like It! I Like It! キミに会えた
I Like It! I Like It! I met you,
ずっと離さないでいてね
so don't ever let me go,
ほら キラキラ 虹みたい
Look, sparkling like a rainbow,
世界は回り出す
the world begins to spin!
Thank you so much!
おぱー！
Opa!
I like Fuwamoco!
We like Calli!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
Please listen to our next song, Je t'aime, Je t'aime!
街角に並ぶ映画のポスター
Movie posters lined up on the street corner
もうこの街にも飽きたわ
I'm already tired of this town
受話器の向こうに溜息を返す
Returning a sigh to the other side of the receiver
“Mon amour pour toi”
"Mon amour pour toi"
ハートのロケットに隠した写真
The photograph hidden in my heart-shaped locket
誰も知らない本気の恋
A serious love that no one knows about
神様は気づいてる
God has noticed
Je t'aime★Je t'aime 叶わない夢なんて見たくないわ
Je t'aime★Je t'aime, I don't want to see any unfulfilled dreams
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is beginning to awaken
“愛してるわ”
"I love you"
クレープに描く愛の傘の下で
Under the umbrella of love drawn on a crepe
止まぬ雨の音
The sound of the unceasing rain
Je t'aime★Je t'aime
空っぽな夜に
Because in an empty night,
仕度は いらないから
I don't need to dress up...
ほんの五分でも
Even if it's just for five minutes,
会いたい
I want to see you.
キャンディーショップも
Even the candy shop,
レコードショップも
and the record shop,
あなたがいないと
are boring
つまらない
without you!
ジャケットのポケットに
In the pocket of my jacket,
入れたままのコインに
with the coin left inside,
かけるわ 恋の行方
I'll bet on the destination of our love.
神様が知っている
Only God knows.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
退屈な恋なんて
I don't want a boring romance,
したくないわ
I don't want it.
あっという間に溺れてく
In the blink of an eye, I'm drowning.
"今がすべて"
"This moment is all that matters"
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before my café au lait
しまうその前に
gets completely cold,
もう一度KISSして
kiss me once more.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
物語に鍵をかけて
Lock the story away...
de jour en jour...
あなたのことばかりを夢見ている
I'm dreaming of nothing but you...
mon amour...
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
叶わない夢なんて
I don't want to see a dream
見たくないわ
that won't come true.
でもロマンス目覚めてゆく
But romance is awakening.
"愛してるわ"
"I love you"
クレープに描く
Under love's umbrella
愛の傘の下で
drawn on a crêpe,
止まぬ雨の音
is the sound of unceasing rain.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
mon amour pour toi
退屈な恋なんて
I don't want a boring romance,
したくないわ
I don't want it.
あっという間に溺れてく
In the blink of an eye, I'm drowning.
"今がすべて"
"This moment is all that matters"
カフェ・オ・レが冷めて
Before my café au lait
しまうその前に
gets completely cold,
もう一度聞かせて
let me hear it once more.
je t'aime ★ je t'aime
ラララ...
La la la...
うわあ！あ、アキちゃん先輩！
Wow! Ah, Aki-chan senpai!
アズキ先輩！
AZKi senpai!
perfect timing!
That last song was... "je t'aime ★ je t'aime"!
What did you think, Ruffians?
A little bit more nostalgic?
Yeah, maybe even a bit melancholic of a song.
You know, some city pop vibes too!
And the choreography was cute too, right?
We hope it made you feel nice and warm and fluffy!
And with the sun setting now...
It's starting to feel a bit romantic almost, right?
I guess it's the perfect time to call up our next guests!
Here we go!
アズキ先輩！アキロゼ先輩！
AZKi senpai! Akirose senpai!
Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourselves!
こ、こ、こ、こ、こんあずきー！AZKiです！
Ko-ko-ko-ko-KonAZKi! I'm AZKi!
はい！ホロライブ1期生の癒し系ハーフエルフ、アキロゼことアキロゼんたーるです！
Yes! Hololive Gen 1's soothing half-elf, Akirose, a.k.a. Aki Rosenthal!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
この4人のステージ！
This four-person stage!
すごい！
Amazing!
アズキ先輩とアキロゼ先輩の歌声がすごく大好きなので
We absolutely love AZKi-senpai and Akirose-senpai's singing voices, so
嬉しいー！
we're so happy!
嬉しい！ありがとう！
So happy! Thank you!
次の曲が、あって、そう、
Yes, we have our next song...
アキ・ローゼンタール先輩とAZKi先輩は、とっても魅力的なお姉さんたちなので！
Since Aki Rosenthal-senpai and AZKi-senpai are such charming older sisters...
あら、そうですか？
Oh, really?
ちょっとこの曲で行こうかなと思いました！
...we thought we'd perform this song!
あらあら。ちょっとね、日も暮れてますし。
Oh my. The sun has set too.
確かにちょっと夕方... ちょっとロマンチックになりましたし。
True, it's evening... It's gotten quite romantic.
ちょっと、ちょっぴりセクシーかも？
Maybe even a little bit sexy?
セクシーかも？セクシーな曲？
Sexy? A sexy song?
そういうことある？ お伺いしたいことがあります。
Is that so? There's actually something we'd like to ask.
アキ・ローゼンタール先輩！えっと、この曲を歌う前に、少し、あの、セクシーなウォームアップ...
Aki Rosenthal-senpai! Um, before we sing this song, could you...
教えてもらってもいいですか？いいですか？
...teach us a sexy warm-up? Is that okay?
セクシーウォームアップ？オッケー！
A sexy warm-up? Okay!
じゃあ、まずセクシーな、え、体を作るために...
Then, first, to get our bodies into a sexy mode...
自分のボディを撫でて！撫でて？撫でて！
Stroke your own body! Stroke it? Yes, stroke!
頭撫で撫で、そこから、足から... 足から！
Stroke your head, and then from your feet... starting from your feet!
撫でる！？撫でて！
Stroke?! Stroke it!
やってみて、やってみて！
Give it a try, give it a try!
恥ずかしい！撫でて... アキ・ローゼンタール先輩みたいに...
This is embarrassing! Stroke... like Aki Rosenthal-senpai...
いいよ！オッケー！いいよ！
Nice! Okay! Looking good!
違う！違うよ！
No! That's not it!
このセクシー、撫でるがセクシーだから... セクシーすぎる！
This stroking is what makes it sexy... It's too sexy!
もこちゃん、もう一回、もう一回！え？こう？
Moco-chan, one more time, one more time! Like this?
ちょっと違うかな？
I think that's a bit different...
AZKiちゃんも何か、セクシーだけど可愛い、ちょっと見たいです！
AZKi-chan, we also want to see a sexy but cute version from you!
え？やっぱ、こうやって...
Eh? Well, I guess like this...
おお、お尻、お尻とか！あらあら！セクシー！
Oh, your hips, like your hips! My, my! Sexy!
尻尾！尻尾、尻尾ふりふりも！
The tail! Shake your tail too!
尻尾ふりふりウォームアップ！ウォームアップ、ウォームアップ！
Tail-wiggling warm-up! Warm-up, warm-up!
フリフリ、フリフリ、フリフリ... オッケー、オッケー！
Wiggle, wiggle... Okay, okay!
いいんじゃない？いいよ、いいよ。ちょっとセクシーになった！
Isn't that great? Good, good. You got a bit sexier!
いい感じになりましたね！
We feel ready now!
はい！じゃあ、次の曲行きましょうか！
Yes! Let's move on to the next song!
それでは、聴いてください！DISCOTHEQUE！
Now, please listen to DISCOTHEQUE!
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
(DISCO LADY DISCO LADY)
(DEEP EMOTION DEEP EMOTION)
SWEETIE DARLIN' 踊りましょう
SWEETIE DARLIN' let's dance
はじける BEAUTY LADY
a bursting BEAUTY LADY
生まれ変わって甘い夢
a reborn sweet dream
そっと彩りたいの
that i want to color softly
グラマラスな くちびる
Glamorous lips
ピンク色の 艶めくネイル
and pink sparkling nails
ガラスの向こう側に 映る
Reflected beyond the glass...
素顔 シュー ルなDays
...is my true face, surreal days
キミだけにSO 見せていたい
I want to show only to you...
心の中 瞳の奥
...what's inside my heart, deep in my eyes
AH 傍にいて欲しいよ
Ah, i want you by my side
月のMIRROR BALL 照らされて
under the moon's mirror ball
MY DARLIN' ねぇ ヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
My darlin' let's fall into a vivid love, won't you?
はじける SEXY BEAUTY
a beauty bursting with sex appeal
生まれ変わって甘い夢
a reborn sweet dream
そっと彩るMY LOVE
gently colored by my love
ほら 世界は変わる
look out! The world is changing!
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
(SEXY FEELING CHU CHU... CHU CHU...)
ドラマティックな情熱
Dramatic passion
褪せない デジャヴ 見続けたくて
I want to keep watching an unfading déjà vu
カラフルなSWEETY STORY
A colorful, sweet story
心深く 刻み込む
engraved heartfeltly
小さな闇が 訪れても
Even if a little darkness comes...
恋の呪文 唱えたなら
...if you recite a love spell...
そう、きっと 果てない空
...then I'm sure in the endless sky...
星屑のSHOWERが 降り注ぐ
...a shower of stardust will fall from the sky
だから HAPPY STATION 目指してゆこう
So let's aim for a HAPPY STATION
50/50 あわせて
combine 50/50
100%以上の愛
to get more than 100% love
揺るぎなくここにあると
it's really here without shaking
私思ってる
I believe
(CHU-LU CHU-LU CHU-LU PA-YA-PA)
ゆらりゆらりシブトク
Swaying and swaying tenaciously,
おさきにグラグラッ
I'm already getting dizzy.
君にありのままを
I wish that you would love me
好きでいてほしいと
just the way I am,
願いは
if my wish...
ステキなら
...could be wonderful.
My Darling もっと一緒に踊りましょう
My Darling, let's dance together more!
Secret Night 素敵な
On a secret night, with a
デコレーション
wonderful decoration.
二人のハートで合図
Signaling with our two hearts,
奏であわせて
let's play in perfect harmony!
My Darling ねぇヴィヴィッドな恋しましょう
My Darling, hey, let's have a vivid romance!
はじける Sexy Beauty
Bursting with sexy beauty!
生まれ変わって甘い夢
Reborn into a sweet dream,
そっと彩る My Love ほら
look, my love gently colors it.
世界は変わる
The world is changing!
Churu Churu Churu Payapa
燃え尽きるわ
It's going to burn out,
この恋たぶん
this love, perhaps.
どんな終幕が来ようと 覚悟してる
Whatever ending may come, I'm prepared for it.
余裕なんて ほとんどない
I have almost no composure left,
必死でしがみついてるだけ
I'm just desperately clinging on.
貴方の目 優しく抱きよせる腕
Your eyes, the arms that gently hold me close...
すべてが すべてが 初めてのFall in loveだったわ
Everything, everything was my very first fall in love.
Kiss me 離さないで
Kiss me, don't let me go.
Kiss me 自然なままで
Kiss me, just as you naturally are.
この不安を拭いとって
Wipe away this anxiety.
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Touch me その指先
Touch me with those fingertips.
Touch me その眼差しで
Touch me with that gaze.
この私を包み込んで
Wrap me up inside.
Please Please Please Please...
愛してる
I love you.
よみがえるわ 昨日の事
Yesterday's events come back to life.
あんなに心が揺れたの 初めてだもん
My heart wavered so much, because it's my first time.
寂しすぎて 時に怖い
Being too lonely is sometimes frightening,
二人で居れないこの時が
when the two of us cannot be together.
雨の朝 暖かな部屋でコーヒー
On a rainy morning, with coffee in a warm room...
大人のフリから
...from pretending to be adults,
本当の大人になれそう
it seems we might become true adults.
Kiss me 危険な程
Kiss me, to a dangerous degree.
Kiss me 甘い口づけ
Kiss me, with a sweet kiss.
この願いを全部叶えて
Grant all of these wishes.
ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ ねぇ...
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Knock me その魂で
Knock me with that soul.
Knock me 窓を叩いて
Knock me, knock on the window.
この私を安心させて
Make me feel at ease.
Please Please Please Please...
愛してる
I love you.
Kiss me
危険なほど
so dangerous,
Kiss me
甘い口づけ
with a sweet kiss.
この
This...
願いを全部叶えて
make all these wishes come true.
ねえ...
Hey...
Knock me
その魂で
with that soul,
knock me
窓を叩いて
hit my window.
この
This...
私を安心させて
reassure me,
please...
愛してる
I love you.
One, two!
Are you ready?
Let's do it!
Please join! Triangle Dreamer!
day by day
日に日に募るの乙女心
my maiden heart yearns more and more.
おんなじクラス
In the same class,
斜め前のおとなしい人
the quiet guy sitting diagonally ahead.
格好良くはない
He's not very cool,
だけど優しい
but he is so kind.
いつも頼れる彼
He's someone I can always rely on.
after school
恋愛相談の帰り道
on our way home talking about romance.
なんだって話せる
The one I can talk to about anything,
親友の女の子
is my best friend who is a girl.
スポーツ万能
She's great at sports,
勉強もできて
excellent in studies,
女子力MAXです！
and her feminine charm is at max!
どこにでもある
It happens everywhere,
よくあること
it's a very common story.
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she says...
「あのね、実は私好きな人がいるの...！」
"You know, actually, there's someone I like...!"
ってちょ、マジで！？
Wait, hold on, seriously!?
三角形
Triangle!
三角形の恋は気まぐれ
A triangular love is fickle.
一瞬で
In an instant...
一瞬でくずれるバランス
in an instant, the balance collapses.
ベタなマンガみたいなフラグ
A cliché manga-like love flag...
まさかね自分が立てちゃうなんて
I never thought I'd trigger it myself,
残念すぎます！
how extremely unfortunate!
三角形
Triangle!
三角形の恋は不安定
A triangular love is unstable.
なんちゃって
Just kidding...
なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
but it's not a story where "just kidding" works.
恋と友情ゆらゆらめいて
Love and friendship sway back and forth,
なんか青春しちゃいます
and it feels like I'm experiencing youth.
わたし困っちゃいます
I'm so troubled by this!
完敗です！
It's a complete defeat!
お似合いすぎるわ勝てっこない
They look too perfect, I stand no chance.
悔しいけど
Though it's frustrating...
とかそんなんじゃなくて本心
actually, that's not it; my true feelings are...
てゆーかすでに
More like, I'm already...
応援モード
in support mode!
むしろ清々しい
In fact, it feels rather refreshing.
だけど彼女は
But she has...
不思議な顔 真剣な目で
a puzzled face and serious eyes.
「そうじゃなくて、私あなたが好き...ゴメン」
"No, that's not it, I like you... sorry."
ってちょ、マジで！？
Wait, hold on, seriously!?
三角形
Triangle!
三角形の恋は気まぐれ
A triangular love is fickle.
一瞬で
In an instant...
一瞬でくずれるバランス
in an instant, the balance collapses.
わたし アナタ 彼女とわたし
Me, you, her and me.
超絶！複雑！百合展開は想定外です！
Extremely complicated! Yuri twist is unexpected!
三角形
Triangle!
三角形の恋は不安定
A triangular love is unstable.
なんちゃって
Just kidding...
なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
but it's not a story where "just kidding" works.
解けないパズル与えたもうた
You gave me an unsolvable puzzle,
神よ恨んじゃいます
oh God, I kind of resent you!
わたし悩んじゃいます
Now I'm so worried!
わたし、悩んじゃいます
I'm so worried...
あー！もう！すごいヤバイ！
Ah! Oh! This is crazy!
好きだよ？好きだけど…って、そういう意味じゃなくって！
I like you? I like you but... wait, that's not what I meant!
だって…女の子同士だし…
Because, you know... we're both girls...
ねえ神様、どうしたらいいの？
Oh, God! What should I do?
わたし、どうしたいの？
What do I want to do?
ヘルプミー！！！
Help me!!!
なんか変だー 愛に国境も歳も性別も関係ない！
Love knows no age, no borders, or no gender!
けど、けど、けど！
But, but, but!
三角形
Triangle
三角形の恋はきまぐれ
Triangular love is always a fickle
一瞬で
One moment
一瞬でくずれるバランス
One moment, the balance falls into pieces
普通の恋
I was dreaming of normal love
夢みてたのに
Even though I dreamed of it
ノーマル設定のわたしじゃ ちょっと無理ゲーすぎます
But for someone set to "normal" like me, this game is way too hard
三角形
Triangle
三角形の恋は不安定
Triangular love is so unstable
なんちゃって
Just kidding
なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding" won't do the trick for this category
彼女のこと
If I could
好きになれたら
Fall in love with her...
なんて妄想しちゃいます
Such a wild idea that would be...
わたしどうかしてます
I think I'm going crazy
行くよー！
Here we go!
おお！うわあ！
Oh! Whoa!
うわあ、見てこれ！すごーい！
Oh my gosh! Look at this! Wow!
浮いてる！浮いてる！すごい！
We're floating! We're floating! This is crazy!
Ruffians、大丈夫？見て！浮いてるよ！
Are you okay, Ruffians? Look! We are floating!
ハーイ！ハロー！
Hi! Hello!
落ちないでね！落ちないで！
Don't fall, okay? Don't fall!
こっちのみんなにすごく近付けたよ！
I can get so much closer to you guys over here!
わあ！すごい、Ruffians！
Wow! Oh my gosh, Ruffians!
うわあ、すごかった！ありがとう！
Wow, that was amazing! Thank you!
Ruffians、ありがとう！
Oh my gosh, thank you, Ruffians!
すごく楽しかった！ちょっと目が回っちゃったけど！
That was so much fun! I got a bit dizzy, though!
うん、でもシャボン玉の動きがすごく速かったね！
Yeah, but the bubble was changing so quickly!
速くていいね！
Oh, nice and fast!
うん、ちょっと面白いシャボン玉ダンスもできたしね！
Yeah, and we got to do the bubble dance, which is a little bit silly!
びっくりした？
But did we surprise you?
うん、みんなの顔をいつもよりさらに近くで見られたよ！
Yeah, and we got to see your faces even more close-up than usual!
うん！
Yeah!
さっき歌った2曲は、おかゆ先輩と一緒の「キミコイ」と…
Well, the last two songs we sang was "Kiss me! Choose me!" together with Okayu-senpai...
…そして、フブキ先輩、ミオ先輩、スバル先輩と一緒の「トライアングル・ドリーマー」でした！
...and "Triangle Dreamer" with Fubuki-senpai, Mio-senpai, and Subaru-senpai!
Ruffians、どうだった？
What did you think, Ruffians?
「キミコイ」はおかゆ先輩とずっと一緒に歌いたかった曲なんだ！
Oh, "Kiss me! Choose me!" is a song that we've always wanted to sing together with Okayu-senpai!
うん、ちょっとセクシーな曲だよね！
Yeah, it's a little bit more sexy song!
ちょっとセクシーな曲だよね、はい！
A bit sexy song, right!
うん！そしてフェスアイドル曲の「トライアングル・ドリーマー」！
Yeah! And "Triangle Dreamer", the festival idol song!
うん、振り付けがすごく可愛かった！Ruffians、まだ息してる？
Yeah, the choreography was so cute! Ruffians, are you still alive?
え、生きてる？
Uh, are you alive?
やった、Ruffians！
Yeah, Ruffians!
先輩たちすごく可愛かったね！わあ！
Our senpais were so cute! Wow!
うん！それにシャボン玉で客席の上を浮いたときは…
Yeah! And when crowd surfing with the bubbles...
うん、すごかった！
Yeah, wow! Oh my gosh!
初めてのことだったね！
It was a first!
今年はいろんな「初めて」があるね！
A lot of firsts this year, right?
うん！
Yeah!
そして、小さなお知らせがあります！
Well, we have a tiny, tiny announcement!
フワモコとしての誕生日だからね！
Oh, you know, as FUWAMOCO, it's our birthday, right?
そう、誕生日！
Yeah, our birthday!
なので、みんなにお知らせしたいことがあります！
And so, we have something we'd like to share with you!
オッケー、いっせーのーで！
Okay, on three!
どうぞ！
Here it is!
ばうばう！FUWAMOCO 2026の誕生日グッズで、二人の誕生日をお祝いする時間だよ！
Bow-wow! It's time to celebrate both of our birthdays with our FUWAMOCO 2026 Birthday Merch!
誕生日記念フルセット！
Birthday Set!
フワモコの生誕グッズ紹介、始まるよ！ばう！
FUWAMOCO's Birthday Merch showcase is starting! Bau!
まずは、私たちのママであるイコモチママが描き下ろしてくれた「ふわふわアイドル☆FUWAWA」と「もこもこアイドル☆MOCOCO」のアクリルスタンドで、ふわふわもこもこなアイドルになっちゃおう！
First, you can become fluffy and fuzzy idols with the "Fuwa Fuwa Idol☆Fuwawa" and "Moco Moco Idol☆Mococo" Acrylic Stands drawn by our Mama, Ikomochi-mama!
通常のアクリルスタンドに比べて結構大きいので、コレクションに加えるのにぴったりだと思います！
They're rather big compared to regular acrylic stands, so we think they'll be a great addition to your collection!
大きめサイズで可愛いアイドルのフワモコアクリルスタンド！
Big-sized and cute FUWAMOCO Acrylic Stands!
次は、お茶目な「えへへえんじぇる☆ラバーマスコット」と「HOEH?!でびる☆ラバーマスコット」です！
Next, we have the silly "Ehehe Angel☆Rubber Figurine" and "HOEH?! Devil☆Rubber Figurine"!
机の上に飾るのにぴったりな手のひらサイズのフィギュアです。
They're palm-sized figures perfect for displaying on your desk.
かわいい衣装のフワモコが手のひらサイズのラバーマスコットになったよ！
FUWAMOCO in cute outfits are now palm-sized rubber mascots!
これが目玉だよ！お出かけカジュアル衣装のフワモコぬいぐるみがついに登場！でも今回は、抱きしめるとおしゃべりもしちゃうんです！
This one is big! We finally have FUWAMOCO plushies in our out-and-about casual outfits! But this time, we also speak when you hug us!
「おしゃべりぱぴー☆FUWAWAぬいぐるみ」と「おしゃべりぱぴー☆MOCOCOぬいぐるみ」です！
It's the "Yappy Puppy☆FUWAWA" and "Yappy Puppy☆MOCOCO" Sounds Plushies!
フレンズのやっぴーぬいぐるみと同じサイズだから、一緒に並べて飾れるよ。
We'll be the same size as our friends' yappi plushies, so you can display them together.
おしゃべりパピーぬいぐるみのフワモコだよ！
I'm the talking puppy plushie, Fuwamoco!
ぎゅっとすると、いろいろ喋るよ！
If you squeeze us, we'll say all kinds of things!
どんなボイスが出るかお楽しみに！
Look forward to what kind of voices will come out!
We have the Fuwawa to GO! Finger Puppet!
Oh!
They both come with one extra Ruffians kigurumi costume...
...you can dress us up in and bring around with you everywhere!
フワワの指パペット！
And Fuwawa's Finger Puppet!
どこでも一緒に連れて行けるサイズで、
They're the perfect size to take with you anywhere...
着せ替えラフィアンズ衣装もあるよ！
...and even include dress-up Ruffians outfits!
Finally, we have two different ASMR Voice Packs!
\"Back from a Fluffy Date\" with Fuwawa, and...
...\"Sweet and Fuzzy Needy Puppy\" from Mococo!
ASMRボイスは、英語と日本語、両方で収録してます！
The ASMR voices are recorded in both English and Japanese!
We made our hearts beat so fast!
Be ready to blush when you take a listen to them!
The merch is separated into two sets...
...Fuwawa's Birthday Merch and Mococo's Birthday Merch!
If you purchase the full set, they come with bonuses...
...including a cheki-style card with a special bonus voice!
グッズはフワワセットとモココセットに分かれています！
The merch is split into a Fuwawa set and a Mococo set!
セットごとに、チェキ風カードと特典ボイスが付きます！
Each set comes with a cheki-style card and bonus voice!
The regular version will have a foil-stamped replica signature and message, so it'll be just as cute!
数量限定セットは、直筆サイン付きだよ！
The limited edition set comes with an autographed signature!
We put lots of love into each and every signature, so we hope you look forward to it!
たくさん愛情込めてサイン書きますね！
We'll put lots of love into signing them!
Please check out the hololive official online shop...
...and look for the link in the description or comment area, okay?
ぜひ、ホロライブ公式ショップにチェックしてください！
Please check them out on the hololive official online shop!
BAU BAU!
What did you think of our birthday merch? Pretty cute, right?
The reservations will go on sale right after the birthday live here ends, so don't forget, okay?
生誕のグッズの予約は、
Reservations for the birthday merch...
...このあと開始しますので、お忘れずにチェックしてください！
...will start right after this, so don't forget to check it out!
Make sure to check the link below, or on the side here! Yes!
And don't forget, okay? We put a lot of love into it, and Icomochi-mama too!
Right after this ends, it's time to...
...GO! GO! GO! Okay?
GO BAU!
We performed a lot of special collab songs with our senpai...
...but there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet, right?
そう、まだ会ってない謎のゲストが一人いるんだよね！
That's right, there's still one mystery guest we haven't met yet!
Well, should we give the Ruffians a hint first?
Ruffians, you're curious, right?
クロちゃ、クロちゃん？
Kuro-cha... Kuro-chan?
That's a guest maybe?
That's our guest maybe?
We will see!
Maybe you should get ready, because you know, they aren't quite as bad as Pero...
...but they can get pretty nasty sometimes!
Mocochyan, that's not kind to be rude to our next guest or anything, right?
Especially before calling them out!
We will see!
Well, let's get them out here then! Who could it be? Who could it be?
せーの、どうぞ！
Ready, go ahead!
わー！来たしん！来たしんよ！
Wow! I'm here! I'm here!
来たしんよー！ちゅっちゅ！
I'm here! Chu chu!
自己紹介お願いします！
Please introduce yourself!
クロちゃんです！わー！
I'm Kuro-chan! Wah!
だしんよー！
Indeed!
はじめまして！
Nice to meet you!
チワワじゃないよ、フワワだよ！
I'm not Chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa!
フワワじゃないよ、モココだよ！
I'm not Fuwawa, I'm Mococo!
二人合わせて、フワモコです！
And together we are Fuwamoco!
BAU BAU!
よろしくお願いします！
We look forward to working with you!
フワモコのわちょわちょバースデーフェスティバルに来てくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Fuwamoco's Wacho-Wacho Birthday Festival!
ハッピーバースデーだしんよ、フワモコ！
Happy Birthday, Fuwamoco!
ちょっとね、えっと...
So... um...
視聴者のラフィアンズはたくさんいると思いますけど、
I'm sure we have many Ruffians watching us, but...
クロちゃんがどんな人なのか説明してもらえますか？
...could you explain what kind of person you are, Kuro-chan?
え、自分でスんの？それ。
Eh? I have to do it myself?
自己紹介！
Self-introduction!
わかったしんよ。だってこれ海外の人も見てますもんね？
Okay then. I mean, we have overseas viewers too, right?
海外の人もわかる自己紹介しますからね。
I'll do an introduction that overseas viewers can understand too!
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you, chu chu chu chu tulip!
Nice to meet you, nice to meet you, chu-chu-chu-chu Tulip!
Tulip!
え？止まらないで？
Eh? Don't stop there!
え？クロちゃん、え？チューリップ？
Eh? Kuro-chan, eh? Tulip?
いや、チューリップ、ノー、ノー。
No, Tulip, no, no.
ちょっとまだわからないかもしれないから...
They might not understand it yet, so...
安田大サーカスっていうトリオを組んでる芸人さんで、
Well, I'm a comedian in a trio called Yasuda Dai Circus...
あと豆柴の大群のプロデューサーもやってます。
...and I also produce the group Mameshiba no Taigun.
作詞とかもしています、クロちゃんです！
I write lyrics too. I'm Kuro-chan!
わー！じゃあ今回は英語でお願いします！
Wow! Now, please do it in English!
え？僕が？
Eh, me?
自分で？
Yourself?
え、そんなこと急に言われたら、It's shy!
Eh, if you tell me so suddenly... It's shy!
言い訳はなし！
No excuses!
人の話聞いてる？
Are you listening to me?
頑張って！
Do your best!
ええと、なんだろう？有名...
Let's see, what is it? Famous...
有名コメディアン！
Famous comedian!
おー！コメディアン！
Oh! Comedian!
あと、アイドルプロデューサー！
And idol producer!
いやいや、かっこいい！やってるしね！
Wow, that's so cool! You actually do that!
できる、できる！
You can do it, you can do it!
クロちゃんテレビでよく見てるけど...
I watch Kuro-chan on TV all the time, but...
フワモコのペット of ペロちゃんと、ちょっと似てるところがたくさんあるね！
...there are a lot of similarities between you and our pet, Pero-chan!
そうそう！
Yeah, yeah!
ちょっと後ろの壁見てくださいね！
Please look at the wall behind us!
そう、それペロです！
Yes, that's Pero!
ちょっと待って、丸いところが似てるだけじゃない？
Wait a minute, isn't it just because we're both round?
違う、違う！
No, no!
クロちゃんと似てるところは、嘘つきで、女の子好きで...
The similarities between you and Kuro-chan are: lying, loving girls...
いやらしい！
...and sleazy!
だから、見た目で騙されないで！
So, don't be fooled by appearances!
え、クロちゃんはそれで大丈夫なの？言われて。
Wait, is Kuro-chan okay with being called that?
いや、ひどい！悲しくなってきた！えーんえーん！
No, that's terrible! I'm starting to get sad! *Crying*
えんぽいぽい、ふん！
*Scoffs*
全然人の話聞かないよね、君たちは。
You girls really don't listen to anyone, do you?
できれば、クロちゃんはペロの友達になってくれませんか？
If possible, Kuro-chan, won't you be friends with Pero?
フワモコの友達じゃなくて、ペロの友達になるの？
Not Fuwamoco's friend, but Pero's friend?!
そう、フワモコはクロちゃんと友達になりたくないから！
Yeah, because Fuwamoco doesn't want to be friends with Kuro-chan!
おかしくない、それ？
Isn't that weird?!
嫌だ、嫌だ！気持ち悪いから！
No way, no way! Because it's creepy!
気持ち悪くない！マニアには受ける！
I'm not creepy! I'm popular with specific demographics!
違う！フワモコ気持ち悪いやっぱり！
No! Fuwamoco still thinks you're creepy after all!
でも、でも、モコちゃん、ちょっとやりすぎですよ、失礼です！
But Moco-chan, that's a bit too much, that's rude.
もし、もしもペロと仲良くなってほしいんだったら、フワモコちゃん、クロちゃんに可愛らしく頼んだ方がいいんじゃない？
If you want me to be friends with Pero, shouldn't you ask me nicely, Fuwamoco?
はぁ！？
What?!
ノー！/ノー！
No! / No!
しっかりとした否定！
A flat-out rejection!
けど、ペロ可愛いから仲良くなってもいいとは思ってるよ。
But Pero is cute, so I think it's fine for us to be friends.
うれしい、うれしい！
Yay, we're so happy!
可愛くないけど、なんか仲良くなってくれたら嬉しいかな！
You're not cute, but we'd be happy if you became friends!
感情が、感情がいろいろありすぎるのよ、本当に。
You have way too many conflicting emotions going on, seriously!
まあ、まあ！
Well, well!
クロちゃんって芸人さんだけど、アイドルになりたいんですよね！
Kuro-chan, you're a comedian, but you want to be an idol, right?
そう、元々アイドルになろうと思ったのに、騙されて芸人にさせられたから。
Yes, originally I wanted to be an idol, but I was tricked into becoming a comedian.
アイドルは本当に夢、ドリーム！
Being an idol is truly my dream!
なんか悲しいな。可哀想。
That's kind of sad. Poor thing...
でもドリームって大事！
But dreams are important!
そう。で、まあ、クロちゃんのドリームはアイドルなんだから...
Right. Since Kuro-chan's dream is to be an idol...
もうせっかく、一緒に歌ってくれませんか？
...since you're here, won't you sing with us?
あ、いいよいいよ！いいよ、オッケーだしよ！
Ah, sure! I'd love to!
一緒に歌えるんだ！
We get to sing together!
どの曲、どの曲？どの曲にする？
Which song? Which song are we doing?
あの、ハードル上げないで。
Please don't raise the bar too high!
大丈夫！
It's okay!
ね、アイドルのプロデューサーもやってるし。
After all, you're also an idol producer.
実力見せてよ！
Show us what you've got!
オッケーだしよ、行くよ行くよ！
Okay then, here we go!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、すごく可愛い曲を一緒に歌いましょう！
Then let's sing a super cute song together!
何、何かな？楽しみ！
What song is it? I'm excited!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、一緒にタイトルコールしましょうね！
Let's do the title call together!
せーの、ちゅ、多様性。
Ready, go! Chu, Tayousei.!
ちゅ、多様性やるの！？
We're doing "Chu, Tayousei."?!
我愛你 酔いが醒めない
I love you, my intoxication won't fade
Oh, I need you 恋が醒めない
Oh, I need you, my love won't fade
お生憎様の 慣れ果て 察して
Have pity on the ruins of this unfortunate soul
無問題 破滅してみて
No problem, try bringing on the ruin
Hold me tight トラウマの味
Hold me tight, the taste of trauma
猛反対 お手 お座り で ハイ 報酬
Fierce opposition! Give me your paw, sit, yes, here's your reward
喉の奥が チクンチクン
Deep in my throat, it's prickling
僕は ドクンドクン
And my heart is pounding
鼓動で孤独 消してみてよ
Try making the loneliness disappear with your heartbeat
愛も恋も 淘汰して
Weed out both love and romance
僕を独占して
Keep me all to yourself
このまま中毒になるまで チューしよ
Let's kiss like this until we become addicted
そして
And then...
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get get get on! Get get get get on chu!
熱く とろけるくらいに 溢れた気持ちが
My feelings overflow so much that they melt hotly
たまらないでしょ
It's irresistible, isn't it?
Get get get on! Get get get on! Get on chu!
Get get get on! Get get get get on chu!
Get on! Get on!
我愛你 無問題
I love you, no problem
Get get get on chu!
ポン・チー・カン 勝負はいつも
Pon, chi, kan! The match is always...
トンチンカン 僕に言わせりゃ
Absurd! If you ask me...
ちんぷんかんぷん だ 最後はロンでしょ？
It's all gibberish. The end is won with a "Ron," right?
もう何回？ 殺されればいい
How many more times must I be killed?
Oh, One night 忘れられない
Oh, one night, I can't forget it
終わんないでトキメキ偏愛予習
Don't let it end, this heart-fluttering rehearsal of devotion
喉の奥がチクンチクン
Deep in my throat, it prickles
僕はドクンドクン
My heart is thumping
心臓ごと 引きずり出して見せてよ
Drag out your very heart and show it to me
きもちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, even if it's a hassle
やっぱ照れくさいけど
It's a bit embarrassing after all, but...
死ぬまで忘れられないチューしよ
Let's share a kiss we'll never forget
いかれた街はゾンビで溢れる
This crazy town is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You are in love with me
トキメク胸に繋がるループを引き抜けよ
Pull out the loop connected to your fluttering chest
Bet bet bet on chu!
本気で狂えるくらいの愛しさが
A love so deep it could truly drive me mad...
美しいでしょ
...is beautiful, isn't it?
Get get get on chu!
Get get get on chu! せーの
Get get get on chu! Ready, set...
ポン・チー・カン 終わんない
Pon, Chii, Kan! It's not ending!
Get Get Get on chu!
我愛你 無問題
I love you, no problem!
Get Get Get on chu!
やった、やった！うまくいったしんよー！
We did it, we did it! It went perfectly, shin!
ありがとう！よかったー！がんばったね、クロちゃん！
Thank you! That was great! You did your best, Kuro-chan!
楽しかった、ありがとう！
That was so fun, thank you!
えっと、さよならする前に、一個お願いしてもいいですか？
So, before we say goodbye, can we ask you for one favor?
一個だけだしんよ？一個だけじゃん！
Only one, okay? Just one!
フワモコは魔界の番犬で、バウバウをよく言ってるんですけど
Fuwamoco are guard dogs of the Underworld, and we often say 'Bau Bau'.
クロちゃん、カメラに向かって、フワモコのように、可愛いバウバウをしてもらえますか？
Kuro-chan, could you face the camera and do a cute 'Bau Bau' like Fuwamoco?
えー？できるかな？いくしんよ！バウバウ！
Eh? I wonder if I can? Here I go, shin! Bau Bau!
えー？それがベスト？もう一回！もっとやって！
Eh? Was that your best? One more time! Do it more!
バウバウ！...可愛いかな？
Bau Bau! ...Was that cute?
実はもう一個やりたいことがあるんですけど
Actually, there is one more thing we want to do...
何？
What is it?
フワモコはいつもやってる自己紹介があって、できれば3人で一緒にやりたいです！
Fuwamoco has our usual self-introduction. We'd love to do it together with all three of us!
あ、あれ可愛かったからやりたい、クロちゃんも！
Oh, that was so cute, I want to do it too!
じゃ、いきますよ！
Alright, here we go!
チワワじゃないよ！フワワだよ！
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa!
ワワワワワワ！フワワじゃないよ！クロちゃんだよ！
Wa-wa-wa-wa-wa! I'm not Fuwawa! I'm Kuro-chan!
クロちゃんじゃないよ！もここだよ！
I am not Kuro-chan! I am Mococo!
ほら、息合わせて！いやいやいや！怒らないで！どうしたの？
Hey, sync up with us! No, no, no! Don't get mad! What's wrong?
出てって、クロちゃん！出ていかないから！なんなのそれ！
Get out, Kuro-chan! I'm not leaving! What is that about?!
もう嘘とかつくよね。謝らないと...
You're lying to us again. If you don't apologize...
もここパイキックしちゃう！
Mococo is going to pie-kick you!
救急車、一台... いらないよ、もう嘘！
Call an ambulance... We don't need one, you're lying again!
痛いってなんなのそれ！ぷんぷん！なんでぷんぷん怒るのちょっと！
I'm hurting, what is with that?! Hmph! Why are you getting huffy?!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて！大丈夫、もこちゃん大丈夫。
Calm down, calm down! It's okay, Moko-chan, it's okay.
クロちゃんはこれからも、みんなをいっぱい笑顔にして、素敵なアイドルになってくださいね！
Kuro-chan, please continue to make everyone smile and become a wonderful idol!
なるしんよ！バウバウ！
I will, shin! Bau Bau!
じゃ、もこちゃん、最後にクロちゃんにハイタッチしてお別れしようね。おっけー。仲直り仲直り？仲直りね！
Well, Moko-chan, let's high-five Kuro-chan to say goodbye. Okay. Making up? Yes, making up!
はい、タッチ！ハイタッチ！ほらほら、ほらほらほら！
High-five! High-five! Come on, come on!
やってみて、やってみて！ほら、やってやって！仲直り、仲直り！ていっ！
Give it a try! Come on, do it! Let's make up! Take that!
あ、逃げちゃった！ひどくない、ちょっと！なんなの？
Ah, she ran away! Isn't that mean?! What is going on?!
フワモコちゃん、本当にお誕生日おめでとうございます！
Fuwamoko, happy birthday, for real!
ありがとう！おめでとうしんよー！キュンからのバッキュン！おめでとうハート！
Thank you! Happy birthday, shin! From a squeeze to a bang! Congratulations heart!
Firework! Purple, blue, yellow fireworks! たまやー！かぎやー！
Fireworks! Purple, blue, and yellow fireworks! Tamaya! Kagiya!
Wow! That was so much fun! Things got a little bit crazy there, not too sure what happened.
もうカオスすぎて、わからなくなってきたかも！
It was so chaotic, I've completely lost track!
But we still have one more... one more very exciting thing to show you! まだまだ楽しみがあるよ！
But we still have one more... one more very exciting thing to show you! There's still more fun to come!
Maybe what it is... can you guess what it is? なにかな、なにかな？ Fuwamoko, our 1st Anniversary!
Maybe what it is... can you guess what it is? I wonder what it is! Fuwamoko's 1st Anniversary!
We released our...
first original song!
which was Bau Bau!!
And then for our first anniversary,
we were able to release Lifetime Showtime!
our original song that's been with us along this journey.
Yeah, a very special song.
And you know, for FuwaMoco,
singing and dancing is something that means so much to us!
Yeah, music!
And, Ruffians, we might have heard
that you'd like to hear more from us too, right?
Right? Yeah! Yeah!
What do you think? Yeah!
Well...
our announcement is...
Drumroll!
Okay, drumroll, Ruffians!
Bau bau bau bau...
Then...
A new original song!
FUWAMOCOの新規オリジナルソング！
FUWAMOCO's brand new original song!
And this song is extra special!
Yes! It's written by none other
than the legendary rock idol song composer,
Matsuoka Kenta-san!
who works with many famous idol groups that we love!
Also, written music for the idol group
that Kuro-chan produces, MAMESHIBA NO TAIGUN-san!
Yeah! But Ruffians, you might be a little bit surprised, okay?
Yeah, so get ready!
Ruffians... with this song,
we'd like to express our ruff-est feelings as demon dogs.
DEMON'S RESIDENCE
「相棒、どこへ行こうか」
"My partner, where shall we go?"
ネオンの脇を抜け
Passing by the neon lights,
バブルガムがはじけたら let's go
Once the bubblegum pops, let's go!
最低な夜を潜って
Diving through the worst night,
僕らは群れをなす
we form a pack.
「あの頃よりもマシだね」 my way
"It's better than back then, isn't it?" My way.
「不完全なんです」首輪をつけた
"I'm incomplete," wearing a collar.
良い子なんかじゃもうイヤ (Ah)
I don't want to be a good girl anymore! (Ah!)
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 噛みついていけ
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, bite down and go on!
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage.
気分はどうだい 泣いているのかい
How are you feeling? Are you crying?
鎖をちぎって
Break the chains!
叫んでいたいんだ stray dogs 遥か
I want to keep screaming, stray dogs, far away...
彼方へと飛ぶ鳥を
towards the distance, at the birds flying.
見上げるだけかい それでいいのかい
Will you just look up at them? Is that enough for you?
燃えるなら ほら 青く
If you're going to burn, look, burn blue!
「説教なんかいらない」
"I don't need a sermon,"
スプレー缶振って
shaking a spray can.
イタズラ書きで彩る runway
Decorating the runway with graffiti.
愛情なんか coin toss
Love is like a coin toss,
誰に bet するのか
who are you betting on?
不確定要素ばかりね lonely
Nothing but uncertain elements, how lonely.
二人でひとつと決めた
The two of us decided to be one.
あの日を忘れない (Ah)
I won't forget that day. (Ah!)
DEMON'S RESIDENCE 満天の空
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, a sky full of stars.
あの星がひどく不快で
That star is terribly unpleasant.
勝利はどうだい 味はするのかい
How is victory? Does it have a taste?
鎖を噛んで
Bite the chains!
唸っていたいんだ stray dogs 僕ら
I want to keep growling, stray dogs, us!
宇宙さえも撃ち落として
Even shooting down the universe.
見下ろす奈落 ビルは輝く
Looking down at the abyss, the buildings shine.
LOL, now I am free!!
Woah-oh-oh-oh woah-oh-oh
孤独を分け合い 食べた
Sharing and eating solitude,
あの日を忘れない
I won't forget that day.
嗚呼
Ah...
夜を睨んだ stray dogs そうだ
Staring into the night, stray dogs, that's right!
怪物は世界のほうさ
The monster is the world itself.
抜け出せるのかい 足は動くかい
Can you escape? Are your feet moving?
走るなら今
If we run, it's now!
DEMON'S RESIDENCE stray dogs 僕ら
DEMON'S RESIDENCE, stray dogs, us!
この街を駆けて行け
Run through this city!
地獄の果てに 何が見えるかい
At the end of hell, what do you see?
鎖をちぎって
Break the chains!
叫んでいたいんだ stray dogs 僕ら
I want to keep screaming, stray dogs, us!
この街は檻のようで
This city is like a cage.
君ならどうだい 共に駆けるかい？
How about you? Will you run with us?
夜明けが合図だ 行こう
Dawn is the signal, let's go!
Bau bau!
Thank you for always being here for FUWAMOCO!
Please listen to...
side by side!
Finally we made it through but not without some tears
With the help of friends so true we faced all of our fears
Now we're here to celebrate all that we have done
I can feel it's more than just a game of fate
'cause our stories have just begun
Hand in hand we're not waiting on tomorrow
From now on its the heart that we will follow
We'll move on passed the heartbreak and the sorrow if you
We'll move on past the heartbreak and the sorrow if you
Stay by my side
Dancing harmonics feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
Even though there's been ruff times where nobody wanted us,
We kept going, and we kept dreaming!
Now we're here, we're not alone anymore!
We'll be here together, we have smiles to protect!
c'mon, let's go
Dancing harmonics feeding the music
as we come alive, and sparks ignite
We're making memories everyday underneath
the summer sky and through the night
We're singing melodies every time we hear music
from inside as hearts collide
Bringing out the best in each other
now we're feeling free like we're meant to be
nya, nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
nya-nya-nya, nya-nya-nya
Bau bau!
Thank you for the encore!
That was side by side!
Bau bau!
We're really happy we got to perform side by side for the first time live today!
うん！初お披露目できてとっても嬉しいです！
Yeah! I'm so happy we got to perform it for the first time!
side by side is a song made by Aiobahn-san, but also, between FUWAMOCO!
Yeah, it is!
You know, we know it's a song that you love a lot, but we also do because...
...it's very special to us, since it's the ending theme for a visual novel that we love...
NEKOPARA!
Bau bau!
And with this song, our dream of singing the opening or ending theme for a visual novel came true!
そう！この曲で、ふわもこの夢、美少女ゲームの主題歌を歌うことが、叶いました！
Yes! With this song, FUWAMOCO's dream of singing a theme song for a bishoujo game came true!
Our dream came true! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
And thank you so much for joining us for our special day again this year!
It's been a dream for us!
And, you know, it's all because of you that we're able to be here, and do all the amazing things that we do, so...
Thank you!
It's sad to say...
This next song... is our last song!
No!
But, like... but... it's a very special one!
You know, FUWAMOCO are demon guards. We're here to protect your smile, right?
We'll continue to do that...
Protect your smile!
Yeah, through our role as idols!
And just as we have fluffy and fuzzy souls, too!
Yeah!
We'll continue to be here for thousands and thousands of demon dog years!
All while remembering that, you know, every day isn't given.
We don't take anything for granted.
And you know, when you're down, we hope that you'll remember that we're always here cheering you on, okay?
Yeah! We're cheering you on, Ruffians!
So, please listen closely to the lyrics of our last song for today.
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too...
あなたが笑ってますように ずっと...
I hope that you'll always be smiling...
lala...
Thank you so much, Ruffians, for spending our birthday with us today!
Please think of this song whenever things go wrong, and know that we'll be here. This last song is for you!
Wishful☆Garnet!
過去を振り返ると 思い出す
When I look back on the past, I remember...
ガーネットの空 溢れてく光
The garnet sky, overflowing with light.
この瞳に映し出されたあの日は
That day, reflected in these eyes,
美しく揺れる
...sways so beautifully.
what do you think?
紅く滲んだ空に
To the crimson-stained sky,
願いました
I made a wish.
どうかこの願い
Please let this wish...
届けてください
...be delivered.
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope that you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are torn apart,
前を向けますように
I hope we can still look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you...
わたしが壊してあげる
...I will break them for you.
もう負けないで進むこと
Keep moving forward without losing anymore,
いつでもそばにいるから
Because I'll always be by your side.
落ち込んだり自信を無くした時だって
Even when you're feeling down or lose your confidence,
目の前にいてくれる
...you are always there in front of me.
あなたの笑顔に何度も
By your smile, so many times,
救われた
...I've been saved.
だから...
And that's why...
so i love you
挫けそうになったら
If you feel like giving up,
手を伸ばして
...reach out your hand.
まだ知らない明日
A tomorrow we don't yet know,
一緒に見つけよう
Let's find it together.
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたを照らしていたい
I want to keep shining on you.
泣きそうになった時は
When you feel like crying,
こっち向いてほしい
I want you to look this way.
世界でひとりぼっち
Don't think that you're...
そんな風に思わないで
...all alone in this world.
愛してくれる人はきっと
The people who love you will surely...
いつもあなたを想ってる
...always be thinking of you.
uh... yeah...
Wishful Garnet!
lala lala... lalala...
Lalala... lalala...
願いました
I made a wish.
どうかこの願い
Please let this wish...
届けてください！
...be delivered!
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope that you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are torn apart,
前を向けますように
I hope we can still look forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you...
わたしが壊してあげる
...I will break them for you.
もう負けないで進むこと
Keep moving forward without losing anymore,
輝く空へ
...to the shining sky.
明日も 明後日も
Tomorrow, and the day after too,
あなたが笑ってますように
I hope that you'll be smiling.
離れ離れになっても
Even if we are torn apart...
前を向けますように
...I hope we can keep looking forward.
あなたを縛る鎖を
The chains that bind you,
わたしが壊してあげる
I will break them for you.
もう負けないで進むこと
To move forward without losing again,
いつでもそばに
I'll always be by your side...
あなたのそばに
...right by your side...
わたしはいつもいるから
...because I will always be there.
ららら...
La la la...
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah...
ばうばう！
Bau bau!
Thank you so much, Ruffians!
We'll see you soon at our Encore Live in membership, okay?
ばうばう！
Bau bau!
メンバー限定アンコールライブで待ってるよー！
We'll be waiting for you at the member-only encore live!